本:传给詹妮,传!投篮!
Ben: Pass it jenny, pass it! Into the basket.
沃特:好,闪开!闪开!
Veto: Hey, I'm open! I'm open!
本:撞他,詹妮.
Ben: Slam it Jenny.
本:嘿,笨蛋!
Ben: Hey, foul.
沃特:嘿,你才是笨蛋!
Veto: Hey you're foul.
詹妮:你这个笨蛋,我要走了,
Jenny: Watch it you pig, dog, wart hog. Ah, got to go. Ballet class.
上芭蕾舞课!很好的项目,本.
Good game Ben.
本:詹妮,你好好去玩吧.我们还得比一下.
Ben: Nice going Jenny. We're still champs.
詹妮:斯汀奇,好好准备吧,下次该看你的了.
Jenny: Stinky, try crocket. You know next time it will be you on your butt.
沃特:谁管呢?你们来参加我的万圣节聚会吗?
Veto: Who cares? So are you guys coming to my Halloween party?
本:你说真的?
Ben: You bet.
沃特:但是你没有RSVP.
Veto: But you didn't RSVP.
斯汀奇:公共场所这样做很可笑.
Stinky: I get smacked if I do that in public.
沃特:别忘了带个客人来,你知道我什么意思.
Veto: Just don't forget to bring a guest, if you know what I mean.
本:你好,妈妈.
Ben: Hi mum.
麦琪:晚上好,先生们!
Maggie: Good evening gentlemen.
斯汀奇:你好,西维尔太太.
Stinky: Hello Mrs. Seaver.
沃特:你!
Veto: Yo!
麦琪:你!
Maggie: Yo!
斯汀奇:西维尔太太怀孕了.
Stinky: Mrs. Seaver's pregnant.
本:成熟点,你这家伙.那完全是人体本能.
Ben: Grow up you guys. It's a perfectly natural bodily function.
小伙子:人体本能!哦!
Kids: Natural bodily function! Oohh!
本:你们小心点.
Ben: Knock it off you guys.
沃特:好的.听着,我得去休息了.再见.
Veto: Yeah yeah. Listen I got to break. See you later.
本:再见.
Ben: See you Veto.
斯汀奇:本,你得告诉我.RSVP表示啥?
Stinky: Ben you've got to tell me. What does RSVP stand for?
本:你不知道?
Ben: Don't you know anything?
斯汀奇:告诉我.
Stinky: Just tell me.
本:RSVP意思是沃特聚会上的茶点.
Ben: RSVP means refreshments served at Veto's party.
斯汀奇:哦!
Stinky: Oh!
麦琪:你爸还和病人在一起吗?
Maggie: Is your father still with a patient?
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
麦琪:不过,我希望他已经把饭做好了.
Maggie: Darn, I was hoping he'd cook dinner.
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
麦琪:你告诉他,说我太累了,做不了饭,好吗?
Maggie: Would you tell him that I am too tired to cook?
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
麦琪:我要去楼上打个瞌睡.
Maggie: I'll be upstairs taking a nap.
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
麦琪:迈克,你一个字也没听我说.
Maggie: Mike, you haven't heard a word I've said.
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
麦琪:迈克!
Maggie: Mike!
迈克:好的,让爸爸做饭因为你太累了,你上楼等爸爸给你道歉.
Mike: Yeah, dad flaked on the cooking and you're tense, so you'll be upstairs waiting
for his apology
麦琪:喔.你在听!
Maggie: Uh. You were listening.
本:但是我不明白.这件化装服真不错.
Ben: But I don't get it. It's a great costume.
你妈为什么不让你穿?
Why won't your mum let you wear it.
斯汀奇:她认为让我穿这种垃圾衣服不合适.
Stinky: She thinks dressing up like garbage is wrong for a kid named stinky.
迈克:你们要谈很久吗?
Mike: Is this going to be a long conversation?
斯汀奇:是的,你要化装成什么?
Stinky: So, what are you going to be?
本:很普通.一个把切肉刀砍在脑袋上,
Ben: My usual. A dead guy with a meat cleaver in his head and eye balls
眼珠突出的死人!
hanging out.
斯汀奇:厉害!我躲在你背后,浑身流满鲜血!
Stinky: Cool. I could be a big bloody boil growing out of your back.
本:好!
Ben: Alright!
迈克:孩子们!过来.
Mike: Guys! Kids kids kids. Come on now.
你们不觉得你们的年龄还太小,不应该搞这些恶作剧吗?
Aren't you a little old for trick or treat?
本:我们不是小孩子,这也不是什么恶作剧.
Ben: We are not kids. And it's not trick or treat. Party at Veto Perducci's.
我们是沃特?浦鲁茨家宴会上的学生客人.
Junior High only.
斯汀奇:那是在马厩里.
Stinky: It's in a horse barn.
本:是的,在沃特宴会上会有很多好东西.
Ben: Yeah, there's going to be plenty of RS at VP.
斯汀奇:游戏,奖品,和lancing(切割).
Stinky: Games, prizes, lancing.
迈克:Lancing?
Mike: Lancing?
斯汀奇:这是个让人激动的点子.
Stinky: That's what gave me the boil idea.
Mike: No no no no. Guys, it doesn't say lancing, it says dancing
本和斯汀奇:哦.
Ben and Stinky: Oh!
迈克:还说你和一个客人.
Mike: And it also says you and a guest.
什么样的女孩会去见让切肉刀砍在脑袋上,
Now what girl wants to be seen with you with a meat cleaver stuck in your
骑小猪回去的发出臭味的男孩呢?
head, and the stink man here riding piggy back?
本:为什么万圣节这样的重要节日,要和女孩扯上关系?
Ben: But why mess up an important holiday like Halloween, with girls?
迈克:你不喜欢女孩?
Mike: I thought you liked girls?
本:有时候喜欢,有时候不.
Ben: Some times I do, sometimes I don't.
迈克:你们最好在后两天里打定主意,不带女孩参加这样的晚会,是不行的.
Mike: Well you better make up your mind within the next two days, because you sure can't go to a boy girl party without a girl.
本:我们该怎么做?
Ben: What are we going to do?
斯汀奇:我想我们可以吻别.
Stinky: I guess we can kiss the boil goodbye.
本:你没听见我哥说的话吗?我们必须带个伴去,
Ben: Haven't you been listening to my brother?
要么就别去.
We have to come up with dates for this party, or just forget it.
斯汀奇:我有办法了,我就打扮成女孩做你的伴.
Stinky: I've got it. I could dress up like a girl and be your date.
本:我才不要带个名叫斯汀奇的伴呢!
Ben: I don't date girls names Stinky.
斯汀奇:可你没有约女孩子.
Stinky: You don't date ant girls.
本:我们到底该去哪里找女孩呢?
Ben: Where the heck are we going to find girls?
斯汀奇:保险起见,我还是回去,
Stinky: To be on the safe side,
试一套我姐姐的衣服.
I'm going to go home and try on one of my sisters dresses.
本:这太搞笑了.
Ben: That's crazy.
斯汀奇:你有更好的主意?
Stinky: You got a better idea?
本:(暗想)我去找迈克.也许他有办法.
Ben: (in his head) Maybe he'll be cute.
本:我在说什么呀?
Ben: What am I saying?
杰森:迈克,你妈妈回来了?
Jason: Mike is your mum home yet?
迈克:嗯!
Mike: Uh hu.
杰森:我没有时间做晚饭,你告诉她了吗?
Jason: And did you tell him I didn't have time to cook dinner?
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
杰森:她在楼上?
Jason: Is she upstairs?
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
杰森:我跟你说话你听见了没有?
Jason: Have you heard a single word I've said?
迈克:你想知道你没有做饭,妈妈是否会因此生气,她很生气.
Mike: Yes, you want to know if mums tense about you blowing off cooking dinner. She is.
杰森:那我去凑和做一顿吧.
Jason: Let me see what I can whip up for dinner.
本:嘿,爸爸.
Ben: Hey dad.
杰森:嗨,本.
Jason: hey Ben. Hey don't spoil your appetite.
肯定对你们的胃口.我要做一顿出色的晚餐,不管自己喜不喜欢.
I'm cooking a wonderful dinner tonight. Whether I like it or not.
本:迈克,你来帮个忙.
Ben: Mike, you've got to help me.
迈克:本,我很忙.
Mike: Ben, I'm busy.
本:你说要带个伴,可我不知道怎么办.
Ben: But you told me that I need a date, and I don't know how.
迈克:过来,本!
Mike: Come on Ben.
每次你问我关于女孩的事情时,你总是以"够了"结束.
Every time you ask me about girls, you always end up saying 'gross'.
本:嘿!我现在是初中生了.
Ben: Hey, I'm in Junior High now.
迈克:那好吧!我想现在该是你可以花心思找个女人的时候了.
Mike: Well alright. I suppose it's about time to give your heart and soul to a foxy female.
本:够了!
Ben: Gross! I mean,
你不能只告诉我如何找个伴吗,
can't you just tell me how to get a date for the party so I won't
因为我不想成为一个坏孩子.
look like a weenie.
迈克:好的,可以.现在听好了,我只说三个字,你准备笔和纸.
Mike: Alright, alright. Now listen up. I'm going to say three words. You got a pencil and paper?
本:准备好了.
Ben: I'm ready.
迈克:很好,找个女孩.
Mike: Ok. Ask a girl.
本:找个女孩.你愿意让我受罪吗?
Ben: Ask a girl. Do you enjoy making me suffer?
迈克:好了,我会帮你的.
Mike: Yeah alright. I'll help ya.
本:太好了.
Ben: Alright!
迈克:听着,第一课!电话是孤独人的最好的朋友.
Mike: Ok, lesson number one. A telephone is the lonely guy's best friend.
本:我不想打那么电话.
Ben: I'm not calling one of those nine seven six numbers.
迈克:哦,不不不,
Mike: No no no no. now think about it.
你现在想一下,你最喜欢谁?
Now who have you got the hots for?
本:提法妮.
Ben: Tiffany.
迈克:很好,那她姓什么?
Mike: Great, now what's her last name?
本:不知道,光知道她叫提法妮.
Ben: I don't know. Her albums just say Tiffany.
迈克:本,加油,想快一点,一个一个打,谁都行.
Mike: Ben comes on. Think shorter. Now uh, call someone. Anyone.
本:喂!斯汀奇,嗨!衣服合适吗?
Ben: Hello stinky. Yeah, how does that dress fit?
杰森:他是大厨师,是心理学家,停!
Jason: He's a master chef. He's a psychiatrist. Stop. You are both right.
你两样都是.不,他实际上是一个丈夫,
No, he's actually a husband dealing with a woman in the midst of a hormone
对付荷尔蒙高峰期的女人.哦,
rush. Oh hi honey.
亲爱的!我希望你收拾一下房间,等待今晚的大餐.
Yes, well I hope you've kept room in there tonight for a big meal.
麦琪:杰森,别开这种玩笑.我没心情.
Maggie: Jason, don't make fun of the way I look. I am not in the mood.
杰森:好……你今天过得好吧?
Jason: Well uh, did we have a good day?
麦琪:历史上没有人怀孕八个月零两个星期,
Maggie: No one in history who is eight months and two weeks pregnant has
还能过得好.
ever had a good day.
杰森:我把历史忘了.
Jason: Forgotten my history.
麦琪:哦!亲爱的,我虽然对你不好,可是我很爱你.
Maggie: Oh honey, I'm being so mean to you and I love you so much.
杰森:哦,没关系,亲爱的,
Jason: Oh that's alright sweetheart. I understand. And I love you too.
我能理解,我也爱你.
Come on, over here now.
来,到这来,你马上会吃到一份特别的晚餐.
You are about to have a very special dinner in no time.
麦琪:别浪费时间做饭,我们还得练习拉马斯助产法.
Maggie: You're wasting your time cooking when we have Lamars to practice?
我的意思是,明天我们有三四个进修课程,
I mean, we have a three hour refresher course coming up tomorrow and we
我们已经十二年没有做这个了.杰森,
haven't done this in twelve years.
有时候,真搞不懂你.
Jason, sometimes I just don't get you at all.
杰森:我以为我会处理好的.
Jason: I think I handled that rather well.
本:上课时我坐在你后面的,你记得我吗?好极了,
Ben: But I sat behind you in class my whole life. You remember me? Great I...
我……喂!找女孩!好主意.
hello? Hello? Ask a girl! Some big advice. Hello, this is Ben Seaver.
喂!我是本?
Please don't hang up.
西维尔,请别挂.我可能是在浪费时间,
I'm probably wasting my time asking,
我想请你陪我参加沃特普?鲁茨家的万圣节晚会,行吗?
but you wouldn't want to go to Veto Purducci's Halloween party with me,
可以?哦!星期五晚上八点我和我爸妈来接你,
would you? You would? Wow.
他们开车,我还小,
It's Friday, my parents and I will pick you up at eight.
够不上开车的年龄,12岁,你多大了?
They're driving, because I am not old enough to. Twelve, how old are you?
36岁!对不起!打错了.
Thirty six! Sorry wrong number.
迈克:怎么样,谁是幸运的女孩?
Mike: So, who's the lucky girl?
本:听着,有三个爸妈不允许约会,
Ben: Well, three girls aren't allowed to date,
四个说她们不能去因为她们有姐姐约过你.
four said they couldn't go because they had older sisters who dated you,
迈克:真的?
Mike: Really.
开萝尔:嗨!
Carol: Hi.
迈克:本,好本,
Mike: Bye. Well Ben, maybe you are just not an on the phone kind of guy.
你也许不能单靠打电话,我的意思是,
I mean maybe they need to see the desperation in your eyes in order to
也许她们看见你的眼睛,才会答应你.
say yes.
本:女孩子怎么了?为什么装得那么矜持,
Ben: What's with these girls? Why do they have to act so weird?
她们就不能学学斯汀奇或者詹妮或者沃特吗?
Why can't they be like Stinky or Jenny or Veto?
开萝尔:很抱歉打断你们,我不喜欢打断别人,
Carol: Excuse me for interrupting.
不过詹妮可是个女孩.
And you know how I hate to interrupt, but uh, Jenny is a girl.
迈克:啊,开萝尔,本竟然要我……
Mike: Uh carol, I believe Ben was asking me for my...
本:闭嘴,迈克,说清楚些.
Ben: Shut up Mike. Tell me more.
开萝尔:坐过去,迈克.好了,本.
Carol: Out of the way Mike. Alright Ben.
本:(暗想)她是个女孩,那不是个大问题,我就照开萝尔和迈克说的做.
Ben: (in his head) She's just a girl, it's no big deal. I'll ask her like Mike and Carol said.
詹妮:怎么回事,本?
Jenny: What is it Ben?
本:我只是在想万圣节要到了……
Ben: I was just thinking about Halloween coming up and...
詹妮:噢,对,你想去建筑工地翻看门人的马桶?
Jenny: Oh yeah, you want to go down to the constructive site to tip over the porter potties?
本:呵呵,这听起来很有趣,不过你听说沃特的晚会了吗?
Ben: Wow, that sounds great. But have you heard about Vetos cool party?
詹妮:这家伙没请我,我可不愿意去.
Jenny: The jerk face didn't invite me and I wouldn't be seen dead there.
本:(暗想)别慌,说下去.
Ben: (in his head) Don't panic, try again.
本:这次他只请了我们男生,
Ben: See, I think he only invited guys,
不过男生都得带个女孩子.
then the guys are supposed to bring the girls.
詹妮:你是说就像舞伴?
Jenny: You mean like a date?
本:对,的确如此.
Ben: Yeah, exactly.
詹妮:唉,谁想和那些掌心出汗的傻小子在一起呢?
Jenny: Ooh. Who wants to hang out with some goony boys with sweaty palms?
本:(暗想)我的吹吹风.
Ben: (in his head) I'm blowing it.
詹妮:况且,万圣节应该是有趣的.
Jenny: Besides, Halloween is supposed to be fun.
本:告诉我你的想法.
Ben: Tell me about it.
詹妮:你想去翻看门人的马桶吗?
Jenny: So you want to tip over the porter potties, or what?
本:詹妮,我得带个伴,可我不认识真正的女孩子,
Ben: Jenny, I got to have a date and I don't know any real girls,
所以我来请你.你想去吗,还是不去?
so I'm asking you. You want to go, or not? Never mind.
都没关系,整件事很傻,我太蠢了.
The whole things stupid, I'm stupid.
詹妮:好吧.
Jenny: Ok.
本:好了?
Ben: Ok what?
詹妮:那我就下次去翻马桶.我和你去.
Jenny: I can tip over toilets another time. I'll go with you.
本:太好了.
Ben: Alright.
詹妮:你别来接我,我去你家找你,
Jenny: But don't pick me up, I'll meet you at your house.
我不愿意有人以为这是一次真正的约会.
I don't want anyone to think this is a real date.
本:我也是.
Ben: Me either. Sucker.
开萝尔:现在是出场时间.
Carol: It's show time.
孩子们:欺骗还是善意?
Kids: Trick or treat?
开萝尔:你们看起来不可爱,你们是什么人?
Carol: Well don't you look adorable. And who are you supposed to be?
男孩:T先生和T女士,傻瓜.
Boy: Mr. and Mrs. T, fool!
开萝尔:好,这些给你,
Carol: Well. Here's some for you and some for you. Enjoy it kids.
这些给你.拿着吧,
And remember when you get home, before you eat any of this candy,
小家伙们,记住回到家里在吃这些糖果之前,
let your parents check every single thing in these bags.
先让你们爸妈仔细检查包里的每一件物品,现在外面有些坏蛋们喜欢毒害小孩子,
You see, there are some very creepy people out there who like to hurt
他们在糖果上放上有害的东西,比如毒药和……
little children, by putting awful things in their candy, like poison and....
孩子们:啊啊啊!
Kids: Ahhhhh!
开萝尔:我说了什么?
Carol: What did I say?
杰森:麦琪,快点,我们的拉马斯课要迟到了.
Jason: Maggie, let's go. We are going to be late for Lamars class.
麦琪:杰森,我不可能像你那么快.
Maggie: Jason, I can never move fast enough for you.
杰森:好的,抓紧时间,抓紧时间,亲爱的.
Jason: It's alright. Take your time. Take your time honey.
麦琪:出发吧,我们已经迟了.再见小伙子们,我们去上课了.
Maggie: Well let's go, we're late. Bye kids, we are going to Lamars.
本:等一等,等一等,
Ben: Wait, wait, wait! You can't leave.
你们不能走,你们得把我送到沃特家,结束以后再接我回来.
You've got to take me to Veto's party, and pick me up when it's over.
杰森:我以为斯汀奇的爸爸会送你们?
Jason: I thought Stinky's dad was driving you.
本:那是在我们有舞伴之前.
Ben: That was before we had dates.
麦琪:舞伴!杰森,他有一个舞伴.
Maggie: Dates! Jason, he has a date.
本:那不是真的舞伴,那是詹妮.
Ben: It's not really a date. It's just Jenny.
麦琪:噢,
Maggie: Oh his first date.
你的第一个舞伴,
Seems like only yesterday that he was playing basketball with his little
昨天你好像还和她一起打篮球.
friends.
杰森:那是昨天,但我不明白你的意思.
Jason: It was yesterday. But I know what you mean.
本:那你们送我们,十点再来接我们.
Ben: So, you'll take us and pick us up at ten?
麦琪:宝贝,我们可以送你,但是我们的课要上到十一点.
Maggie: Honey, we can take you, but we're in class until eleven.
本:但是你们一定要,一定要,一定要.
Ben: But you got to, you got to, you got to.
开萝尔:本,放松点,别激动.
Carol: Ben, relax and have a carrot.
杰森:这点上我对你妈也没办法,本,她脾气很暴躁.
Jason: I wouldn't push your mum on this Ben. She's a wee bit touchy.
本:妈妈!
Ben: Mum!
杰森:嘿,我们为什么不让迈克来接你们呢?
Jason: Hey, why don't we have mike pick you up?
麦琪:小和尚的第一次约会.
Maggie: My little monk's first date.
本:妈妈你别这样,我只是约了詹妮?弗斯特,她只是我们一起玩耍的朋友,那不是约会.
Ben: Mum, please don't start crying for the kajillionth time. This is just Jenny Foster; she is just somebody I get dirty and sweaty with. This is not a date.
(门铃响)
(Door bell)
詹妮:有人开门?
Jenny: Would somebody open the door.
本:拉好裤子.
Ben: Keep your pants on.
(本在想)那是一次约会.
(In Ben's head) It's a date.
本:再见,爸爸,谢谢.
Ben: Bye dad. See you, thanks.
詹妮:本,怎么回事?
Jenny: Ben, what's going on?
你没和你妈说我们并不是在进行可笑的约会吗?
Didn't you tell your mum we weren't on some stupid date?
本:说了.
Ben: Well yeah.
詹妮:那她为什么还这样看着我们,不停地说"很好,很好,我的,我的."
Jenny: Well how come she keeps looking at us and crying and saying "well well well, and my my my"?
本:我不知道,她怀孕了.
Ben: I don't know, she's pregnant.
爸爸说怀孕的女人要比平时古怪.
My dad says that makes her even more nuts than usual.
浦鲁茨太太:你们好,黑暗中的人们.
Mrs. Perducci: Hello creatures of the dark.
本:你好,浦鲁茨太太.
Ben: Hello Mrs. Perducci.
浦鲁茨太太:你们认识我,觉的我的化装服怎样?
Mrs. Perducci: You recognized me. What do you think of my costume?
本:好极了,看起来非常好.
Ben: They look great. It looks great.
浦鲁茨太太:这是你的小舞伴.
Mrs. Perducci: And this is your little date.
詹妮:不是.
Jenny: No.
本:是的.
Ben: Yes.
浦鲁茨太太:很可爱,很有趣.
Mrs. Perducci: How cute. Have fun.
詹妮:你为什么回答是呢?
Jenny: What did you say yes for?
本:因为,因为这是一次大聚会,我不想被踢出去.
Ben: Because, because this is a big party and I don't want to get kicked out.
詹妮:哦,我以为你有其他想法.
Jenny: Oh. For a second there, I thought you meant it.
本:没有.
Ben: No.
斯汀奇:嗨,你们好,我的舞伴,猜猜我是谁?
Stinky: Hey you guys. Meet my date. Guess what I am?
詹妮:一个孤苦伶仃的男孩.
Jenny: A very lonely boy.
斯汀奇:不,我是个电视传道师.
Stinky: Nope. I'm a TV evangelist.
沃特:唱吧,唱吧,唱吧,唱吧,唱吧.
Veto: Make out song, make out song, make out song, make out song, make out song.
斯汀奇:我们呢?
Stinky: Shall we?
本:(暗想)保持安静,别紧张.
Ben: (voice in his head) Be calm, be cool.
本:我们可以跳舞.
Ben: We could dance.
詹妮:够了.
Jenny: Grosse.
本:(暗想)哦,不.
Ben: (voice in his head) Oh no.
詹妮:那就跳吧,免得一些白痴来找我,在我耳边流口水.
Jenny: We better. Before some jerk face asks me and tries to drool in my ear.
本:(暗想)她对我有意思了.
Ben: (voice in his head) She's crazy about me.
索尼娅:欢迎来到拉马斯,我是教练员索尼娅?奥尔森?普勒恩,我将指导你们自然分娩的好处拉马斯助产法让你们顺利的生产.请吧.
Sonia: Welcome to Lamars. I'm your instructor, Sonia Olsen Puleren, and I'll be your tour
guide on the thrilling adventure of natural child birth. Yes
女士:有医生讲解吗?
Lady: Will any doctors be speaking?
索尼娅:哈哈.没有医生比我更了解这个.大多数的分娩甚至不需要医生.依我的经验,大多数的医生憎恨拉马斯,因为你们懂得越多,你们就越不需要他们.
Sonia: Ah ha ha. There isn't anything a doctor can tell you about this experience, that I can't. Your doctors aren't even going to be there for most of the labor. You see most doctors, in my vast experience, resent Lamars because the more you know, the less you need them.
杰森:啊噢.
Jason: Ah Hu hu hu..
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
索尼娅:你有问题?
Sonia: You have a question?
杰森: 只是关于一句话.你知道,我碰巧就是一位……
Jason: Well more of a statement actually. You see I happen to be a...
麦琪:杰森!你不必和她和就医生的观点争论.
Maggie: Jason! You do not need to get into a debate about this woman's
我们来这儿是学拉马斯助产法的.
opinion of doctors. We're here to study Lamars. Period.
如果你爱我的话,
If you have any love for me at all, you will not,
就别这样,千万别对大家说你是个医生.
I repeat not tell anyone you are a doctor.
索尼娅:哦,先生.你刚才说你刚好是……
Sonia: Yes sir. You were saying you happen to be a...
杰森:是,嗯,一个机械师.我希望大家都知道.
Jason: Be a uh, mechanic. And I just wanted everyone to know.
普鲁茨太太:好了.现在让我来试范吧.
Mrs. Perlucci: Alright. Now let me inspect your cores.
本:我们做得不错.
Ben: We did pretty good, hu?
詹妮:你亲了我的脸.
Jenny: You bit my cheek.
本: 对不起.我太激动了.
Ben: Sorry. I got excited.
詹妮:我们找一些吃的吧.
Jenny: Let's go get some punch.
本:好的.
Ben: Sure.
詹妮:哦,老天.他在那儿.靠近桌子的右手边.
Jenny: Oh my gosh. There he is. Right next to the punch bowl.
本:谁?
Ben: Who?
詹妮:沃特?普鲁茨.我好看吗?
Jenny: Veto Perlucci. How do I look?
本:你怪我没告诉你?我只是因为你看起来……
Ben: You mean I didn't tell you? Boy I should have because you look...
詹妮:本,给我帮个忙吧?
Jenny: Ben, would you do me a favor?
本:你说.
Ben: You name it.
詹妮:过去问他喜不喜欢我.
Jenny: Go ask him if he likes me.
本:谁?
Ben: Who?
詹妮:沃特.
Jenny: Veto.
本:沃特.你刚才还说他是一个笨蛋.
Ben: Veto. You said he was a jerk face.
詹妮:告诉他我也喜欢他.好的,
Jenny: Tell him I like him too. Ok. But only after he says he likes me.
但是只能在他说喜欢我之后.明白吗?
Got all that?
本:(暗想)但是詹妮可是我的舞伴.
Ben: (voice in his head) But she's my date.
本:好的,没问题.
Ben: Sure. No problem.
詹妮:你真好,本.
Jenny: You're a buddy Ben.
本:(暗想)为什么我要这样做.
Ben: (voice in his head) Why am I doing this.
沃特:我要杀了你这只狗.
Veto: Die you dog.
本:沃特,你杀了和尚,得下地狱.
Ben: Veto, you kill a monk, you go to hell.
沃特:嗨.不要说妈妈的坏话.很有趣吗?
Veto: Hey shhhh. Don't cuss with my mum around. Great party hu?
本:还行.我问你,你觉得詹妮?弗斯特怎样?
Ben: Sort of. I'm supposed to ask you what you think of Jenny Foster.
沃特:哦.我看到你带她来了.找不到真正的舞伴吧,嗨,西维尔?
Veto: Oh yeah. I noticed you brought her. Couldn't get a real date hey Seaver?
本: 詹妮是真正的舞伴,我的舞伴.
Ben: Jenny is a real date. My date.
沃特:那你还来问我是否喜欢她?
Veto: Well then how come you're asking me if I like her.
本:我不知道.不过你得说一下喜欢还是不喜欢?
Ben: I don't know. But just do you like her or not?
沃特:绝不!
Veto: Heck no.
本:太好了.
Ben: Great.
沃特:她这样打扮想勾引谁?她以为她打篮球打得好,
Veto: Who's she trying to kid in that dress?
其实很臭,你明白.
She thinks she's so cool about basket ball and stuff and she really stinks
她长得这么丑,我都想吐.
you know. She's so butt ugly, she makes me barf.
本:你看起来真蠢.
Ben: You're as dumb as you look.
沃特:哦,我看起来蠢?
Veto: Oh, I look dumb?
本:是的,你压根配不上詹妮.
Ben: Yeah, you're not good enough for Jenny.
沃特:嗨.你已经喜欢她了.
Veto: Hey. You've got the hots for her.
本:我没有.
Ben: I do not.
沃特:那你为啥暴跳如雷?
Veto: Then why are we fighting?
本:我不知道,我们只是说笑而已.
Ben: I don't know. We're kids.
詹妮:他喜欢我吗?
Jenny: Well, does he like me?
本:你真的想知道?
Ben: You really want to know?
詹妮:当然,说吧,说吧,说吧.
Jenny: Yeah, tell me tell me tell me.
本:(暗想) 我这就告诉你.
Ben: (voice in his head) I'll tell you alright.
本:当然他喜欢你.
Ben: Of course he likes you.
詹妮:我早就知道,我早就知道.别人想什么,我能感觉出来.
Jenny: I knew it, I knew it. I'm very sensitive to what people are feeling.
本:我可没这种本事.
Ben: I wouldn't be too sure of that.
沃特:晚上好,美人儿.
Veto: Evening fair lady.
本:你,罗宾.我只说一句,无论你想怎样,别告诉詹妮,你真的讨厌她.
Ben: Yo, Robin. A word. Whatever you do, don't tell Jenny you really hate her.
沃特:实际上我喜欢她.
Veto: Actually I kind of like her.
本:好,很令人信服.
Ben: Good, very convincing.
沃特: 不,我说真的.
Veto: No, I mean it.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
沃特:刚才我考虑了你说过的话.
Veto: Well what you said made me think.
也许应该冷静地对待一个能打球的女生.
Might be cool to go out with a chick who can dribble.
本:行了.你一开始讨厌她,然后又说喜欢她!
Ben: Hold it. First you hate her, then you like her!
沃特:嗨,我是意大利人.
Veto: Hey, I'm Italian.
本:但是你说过她丑啊.
Ben: But you said she was butt ugly.
本:嗨,西维尔.你说的不过是我的一种手段.
Ben: hey, watch it Seaver. You are talking about my main squeeze.
本:(暗想)他的手段.怎么回事?好,好,好,我已经没法控制了.嗨,死鬼.
Ben: (voice in his head) His main squeeze. How did that happen? Yeah yeah yeah. Where did I lose control of this? Hi Dirk.
斯汀奇:嗨,本.
Stinky: Hi Ben.
本: 嗨,斯汀奇.
Ben: Hi Stinky.
斯汀奇:我们也应该同舟共济.
Stinky: We're going to sit this one out too.
索尼娅:宫颈扩大到八公分了,已经十公分了.
Sonia: This is eight centimeters dilation. This is a full ten centimeters.
现在是……
Now at this point..
甲男士:老兄,我发现在这能学到的东西已超出我的预计了.
Man: Boy, I'm finding out a hell of a lot more than I wanted to know.
杰森:人体的知识总会让我兴奋.我意思是心,
Jason: The human body never fails to excite me.
肝和大脑.它们一起运行,
I just, I mean the heart, the lungs, the brain.
就像一台上了油的机器.
The way they all move together like a well oiled machine.
尤其是女性的生殖系统,那是最神奇的了.
And then the female reproductive system, the most miraculous of all.
那真是……,喔.
It's just... Wow.
甲男士:我应该早点来这学.
Man: I think I'm going to give this a go here.
甲女士:啊!
Lady: Ah!
甲男士:怎么了?宝贝?
Man: What? What honey?
甲女士:啊!
Lady: Ah!
索尼娅:什么事?
Sonia: What is it?
甲女士:我要生了.
Lady: I'm having a baby.
乙女士:我们这儿的人都要生.大人物!
Other lady: We're all having babies here. Big deal.
甲女士:我要生了.啊!现在!
Lady: I'm having a baby. Ah! Now!
乙女士:我的天!(甲男士晕倒)
Other lady: My husband. (Man faints).
索尼娅:怎么了.你真的要生了?
Sonia: Excuse me. You're really in labor?
甲男士:要不要做人工呼吸,或者其他什么?
Man: Isn't she supposed to breathe, or something?
甲女士:相信我,宝贝,我在呼吸呢.
Lady: Believe me honey, I'm breathing.
乙男士:要作引导吗?
Other man: Isn't she supposed to push?
乙女士:他晕倒了.
Other Lady: he's fainted.
索尼娅:好了.大家保持冷静.你们好好地待着这儿,我去找个医生来.
Sonia: Alright. Would everyone just calm down. You just stay right where you are and I'll go call a doctor.
杰森:我可以充当一下医生了吗?
Jason: Can I be a doctor now?
麦琪:当然.你还等什么?
Maggie: Of course. What are you waiting for?
杰森:不好意思,我来帮她.
Jason: Excuse me. I can help here.
丈夫:嗨,伙计.这不是一件润滑剂的工作.
Husband: Hey buddy. This isn't a lube job.
杰森:冷静点.
Jason: Just be calm.
丈夫:在你反常的尖叫之后,你有些发神经了.
Husband: After your pervert rant, you've got a nerve.
麦琪:我认为我们应该做一下申明.我老公并不是一名机修师.
Maggie: I think we should clear something up. My husband isn't really a mechanic.
乙男士:那你怎么告诉我老婆她是否需要一个新的火花塞呢?
Other man: Why did you tell my wife if she ever needs new spark plugs?
杰森:让我查一下你的子宫.
Jason: Let me check your dilation.
丈夫:嗨,你这只猴子.别碰我的老婆.
Husband: Hey you grease monkey. Get your hands off my wife.
所有人:啊!
Everyone: Ahhh!
本:我知道了一件事,两个彼此厌恶的人,
Ben: And the next thing I know, two people who make each other sick,
却会在一起.我真搞不懂.
can't be pried apart. I don't get it!
迈克:听着,本.
Mike: Well look Ben.
如果只和喜欢的人出去,
If people only went out with people that they liked,
那么最终只能结婚,这就没意思了.
then dating would end up in marriage and people wouldn't have any fun.
本:詹妮很快就会发现沃特不适合她.我再也不约会了.
Ben: She's going to find out real soon that Veto's not the guy for her. I'm never dating again.
迈克:你考虑的太多了.
Mike: Well you're sure dressed for it.
本:算了,开个玩笑.
Ben: Go ahead, make jokes. I'm through with dating.
我已经结束约会了,我发现斯汀奇的想法很对.
As far as I can tell, Stinky has the right idea.
迈克:本,本加油.现在你已经骑上了马.
Mike: Ben. Ben comes on. Now you got to get back on that horse.
本:和马有什么关系?
Ben: What do horses have to d with this?
迈克:我说的是女生.
Mike: I'm talking about girls.
本:还是谈马吧.
Ben: Let's talk about horses.
迈克:本,你真的做了一件好事,满足了詹妮的感情,即使她甩了你.
Mike: Ben, it's a really nice thing you did, sparing Jenny's feelings. Even if she did dump on you.
嘿,如果每一个女孩都甩了我,
Hey, where do you think I'd be if I let every girl that dumped me...?
你认为我会怎么样?
I mean uh.
本:你真的被女孩甩过?
Ben: Are you actually saying that girls dumped you?
迈克:嘘.你疯了?想听实话吗?
Mike: Shhhh. Are you crazy? The truth?
本:当然.
Ben: Yeah.
迈克:好的.可能是一次,或者两次,最多不过六次.
Mike: Alright. Maybe once or twice. Half a dozen times tops.
本:真的?
Ben: Really?
迈克:是的.看见那个女孩了吗?她喜欢你.
Mike: Yeah. See that girl over there? She likes you.
本:哪个?
Ben: Who?
迈克:那个护士.
Mike: The nurse.
本:你怎么知道的?
Ben: How can you tell?
迈克:她在看你.每一分钟都在傻笑,
Mike: Well, she's watching you.
然后转身.
Any minute now she's going to giggle and turn away.
本:喔!
Ben: Wow!
迈克:所以请她跳舞吧.
Mike: So ask her to dance.
本:我?不行.
Ben: Me? Uh, no way, um.
女生:嗨!
Girl: Hi.
本:嗨!
Ben: Hi.
迈克:这是本,你是
Mike: This is Ben, and you are...
女生:莫莉.
Girl: Molly.
迈克:本.
Mike: Ben,
本:你,嗯,想,嗯,跳舞吗?
Ben: Would you, um, like to to, um, dance?
莫莉:可以
Molly: Oh yeah.
迈克:那么跳吧.
Mike: So dance.
戴维:下来,下来,真是胆战心惊,下来!
Devil: Get down, get down, get funky, get down!
本:我又骑上马了.
Ben: I'm back on that horse.
迈克:一个爱情傻瓜.
斯汀奇:说得对.
00:21:38,400
Mike: A fool for love. Stinky: You said it.